Guide to the Auditing Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Auditing Office, Yale University, records
1931-1993
RU 169
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
179.25
The records consist of reports, subject files, and memoranda of the Yale Auditing Office. The records document salaries, investments, fellowships, building and maintenance funds, insurance, payroll and benefits, and research expenses.
Yale University. Auditing Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-E (YRG 5-E), Auditing records of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted to the office of origin only.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of reports, subject files, and memoranda of the Yale Auditing Office. The records document salaries, investments, fellowships, building and maintenance funds, insurance, payroll and benefits, and research expenses.
Auditing, Internal; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University. Auditing Office
- Records, 1973-1980; Accession 1981-A-044
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
  Scope and Contents
  Boxes 1-3 transferred to YRG 5-F.
  - Inventory AR-F/76-l2 l2BA MB and B Physical Inventories as at Jan 31, 1974 Fiscal 1976, January 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16 - 17)
  - Inventory AR-F/76-8 l2HA Central Stockroom Physical Inventory at Feb 28, 1975 Fiscal 1976, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Inventory AR/F-76-5 l2XX Review of Yale Printing Service Inventory as at June 30, 1975 Fiscal 1976, January 1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Inventory 12XX STandard Cost System Proposal University Inventory Policy - F/1976 and Standard University Inventory Policy (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bldgs. Under Constr. AR~F/76-21 l5CA Review of Contractor Billing for Change order work at Vanderbilt Hall totalling $25,284 Fiscal 1976, April 1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Accounts Payable 26XX Problems with Royal andADS Checks and Reduction in Payments of same Fiscal 1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Rentals AR-F/76-B 52XX Follow-up Audit Reports F/75-I3 Review of Apartment Rental Income at Divinity School Fiscal 1976, 1975 December (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Building Rentals 57BA Review of Rentals at Low or No Cost Fiscal 1976, November 1975 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Parking AR-F/76-19 57EA Review of University Health Services Visitor's Parking Lot FUAR Fiscal 1976, February 1976 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Sale of Materials NRI 57JA Surplus and Scrap Sales - Procedures and Problems Fiscal 1976, July 1975 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Materials AR-F/76-6 66AA Review of Selected Procedures and Controls - Dept. of Chemistry Fiscal 1976, 1975 December (Box 6, Folder 46 - 49)
  - Dues and Memberships 82EA Review of Dues, Professional Memberships and Professional License Fees Fiscal 1976, June 1976 (Box 7, Folder 54 - 55)
  - Postage AR-F/76-22 82GA Review of the Need for a Postage Application Center Fiscal 1976, April 1976 (Box 7, Folder 56 - 58)
  - Postage AR-F/76-22 Add'l W/p's (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Losses 85FA Investigation of Theft Reports Fiscal 1976 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Equipment 87XX Property Control Procedures for other Universities and for Government Property Fiscal 1976, July 1975 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Time Sheets - Fiscal 1976 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Contracts (1. of 2) Misc. Review of Architectural, Engineering and Construction Contracts - F/76 Fiscal 1976 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Preliminary Review of F/76 Financial Statements - Treasurer's Report - Misc. (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Contracts (2 of 2) Misc. Review of Architectural, Engineering and tonstruction Contracts - F/76 Fiscal 1976 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Cash AR-F/76-25 OlXX Night Depository and Safekeeping Procedure Fiscal 1976, June 1976 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30,. 1979 Trial Balance (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30, 1979 Assets (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30, 1979 Internal Audit (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30, 1979 Inventory (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30, 1979 Income (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30, 1979 Expense (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30, 1979 Liabilities (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1978 to June 30, 1979 Procedural Test (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Yale University Press July 1, 1977 to June 30, 1978 Binder G: Internal Audit (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Yale University Press Fiscal 1978 Binder A - Trial Balance/FinancialStatements (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Yale University Press Fiscal 1978 Binder B - Assets (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Yale University Press Fiscal 1978 Binder D - Liabilities (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Yale University Press Fiscal 1978 Binder E - Profit and Loss (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Yale University Press Fiscal 1978 Binder F - Procedural Tests (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1979 Binder I (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1979 Binder II (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1978 Binder I (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1978 Binder II (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1977 Binder I (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1977 Binder II (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1976 Binder A (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1976 Binder B (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1975 Binder II, Pledges and Reserves (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1975 Binder II, Income and Expenses (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1975 Binder I, Report, Program, Misc. (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Fiscal 1975 Binder IV, Procedural Tests (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Confirmations Pledges Receivable 6/30/75 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Graduate Professional Student Senate Fiscal 1978 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Graduate Professional Student Senate Fiscal 1977 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Sheffield Scientific School Fiscal 1979 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Sheffield Scientific School Fiscal 1978 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Sheffield Scientific School Fiscal 1977 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Sheffield Scientific School Fiscal 1976 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Sheffield Scientific School Fiscal 1975 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Sheffield Scientific School Fiscal 1974 (Box 12, Folder 137)
- Records [microfilm], 1971-1977; Accession 1981-A-045
  - Detailed transactions fund order, Fiscal 1973 (Box 1)
  - Summary statements department order, Fiscal 1973 (Box 1)
  - Transactions, acct. balances, assets and liabilities, July-December 1972, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Detailed transactions department order, Fiscal 1973 (Box 2)
  - Summary statements fund order, Fiscal 1973 (Box 2)
  - Transactions, acct. balances, assets and liabilities, January-June 1973 (Box 3)
  - Consolidated statements, Fiscal 1971-72 (Box 3)
  - Summary statements department order, Fiscal 1973 (Box 3)
  - Detailed transactions department order, Fiscal 1974 (Box 4)
  - Consolidated statements
    - 6/1/1971, Jun-Dec 1972 (Box 4)
    - Jan-May 1973 (Box 4)
    - 1973 Jun (Box 4)
    - 1973 Jul (Box 4)
    - 1973 Aug (Box 4)
    - Sep-Dec 1973 (Box 4)
    - Jan-May 1974 (Box 4)
    - 1974 Jun (Box 4)
    - 1974 Jul (Box 5)
    - Aug-Dec 1974 (Box 5)
    - Jan-May 1975 (Box 5)
    - 1975 Jun (Box 5)
    - July-Dec 1975 (Box 5)
    - Jan-May 1976 (Box 5)
    - 1976 Jun (Box 5)
    - Jul-Nov 1976 (Box 5)
  - System parameter, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Transactions, acct balances, assets and liabilities
    - Jul-Aug 1973 (Box 6)
    - 1973 Sep (Box 6)
    - Oct-Dec 1973 (Box 6)
    - 1974 Jan (Box 6)
    - 1974 Feb (Box 6)
    - Mar-May 1974 (Box 6)
    - 1974 Jun (Box 6)
    - Jul-Aug 1974 (Box 6)
    - Sep-Dec 1974 (Box 6)
    - Jan-Har 1975 (Box 6)
    - 1975 Apr (Box 6)
    - 1975 May (Box 6)
    - 1975 Jun (Box 6)
    - Jul-Sep 1975 (Box 6)
    - Oct-Nov 1975 (Box 6)
    - 1975 Dec (Box 6)
    - Jan-Feb 1976 (Box 6)
    - Mar-May 1976 (Box 7)
    - 1976 Jun (Box 7)
    - July-Oct 1976 (Box 7)
    - 1976 Nov (Box 7)
  - Misc. transactions Endowment Fund, 1905 May (Box 7)
  - Year end data, 1905 May (Box 7)
  - Hierarchy budgetary units (Box 7)
  - I.B.M. payments, 1971-1973 (Box 7)
  - Royal payments, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Royal payments, 1971-72 (Box 7)
  - Royal and I.B.M. payments, 1974-75 (Box 7)
  - Vendor payments, Fiscal 1973-74 (Box 7)
  - Vendor payments, 1975-76 (Box 7)
  - Summary statement fund order
    - 1974 Jul (Box 7)
    - Aug-Sep 1974 (Box 7)
    - 1974 Oct (Box 7)
    - 1974 Nov (Box 7)
    - 1974 Dec (Box 7)
    - 1975 Jan (Box 7)
    - 1975 Feb (Box 7)
    - Mar-May 1975 (Box 7)
    - 1975 Jun (Box 7)
    - 1975 Jul (Box 7)
    - Aug-Nov 1975 (Box 8)
    - 1975 Dec (Box 8)
    - Jan-May 1976 (Box 8)
    - 1976 Jun (Box 8)
    - 1976 Jul (Box 8)
    - Aug-Dec 1976 (Box 8)
    - Jan-Feb 1977 (Box 8)
  - Summary statement department order
    - 1974 Jul (Box 8)
    - Aug-Dec 1974 (Box 8)
    - 1975 Jan (Box 8)
    - Feb-Apr 1975 (Box 9)
    - 1975 May (Box 9)
    - 1975 Jun (Box 9)
    - July-Sept 1975 (Box 9)
    - Oct-Nov 1975 (Box 9)
    - 1975 Dec (Box 9)
    - Jan-Feb 1976 (Box 9)
    - Mar-May 1976 (Box 9)
    - 1976 Jun (Box 9)
    - July-Aug 1976 (Box 9)
    - 1976 Sep (Box 9)
    - 1976 Oct (Box 9)
    - Nov-Dec 1976 (Box 9)
    - 1974 May (Box 9)
    - Jan-Feb 1977 (Box 10)
  - Detailed transactions department order
    - 1974 Jul (Box 10)
    - 1974 Aug (Box 10)
    - Sep-Dec 1974 (Box 10)
    - 1975 Jan (Box 10)
    - 1975 Feb (Box 10)
    - Mar-May 1975 (Box 10)
    - 1975 Jun (Box 10)
    - 1975 Jul (Box 10)
    - 1975 Aug (Box 10)
    - 1975 Sep (Box 10)
    - 1975 Oct (Box 10)
    - Nov-Dec 1975 (Box 10)
    - Jan-March 1976 (Box 10)
  - Detailed transactions state department
    - 1976 Apr (Box 10)
    - 1976 May (Box 10)
    - 1976 Jun (Box 10)
    - Jul-Aug 1976 (Box 11)
  - Detailed transactions department order
    - Sep-Oct 1976 (Box 11)
    - Nov-Dec 1976 (Box 11)
    - Jan-Feb 1977 (Box 11)
    - Jan-Mar 1974 (Box 11)
    - 1974 Apr (Box 11)
  - Detailed transactions fund order
    - 1973 Jul (Box 11)
    - 1973 Aug (Box 11)
    - Sep-Dec 1973 (Box 11)
    - Jan-Feb 1974 (Box 11)
    - 1974 Mar (Box 11)
    - 1974 Apr (Box 11)
    - 1974 May (Box 11)
    - 1974 Jun (Box 11)
    - Jul-Aug 1974 (Box 11)
    - 1974 Sep (Box 11)
    - Oct-Dec 1974 (Box 11)
    - Jan-May 1975 (Box 11)
    - 1975 Jun (Box 11)
    - 1975 Jul (Box 12)
    - 1975 Aug (Box 12)
    - Sep-Oct 1975 (Box 12)
    - Nov-Dec 1975 (Box 12)
    - 1976 Jan (Box 12)
    - 1976 Feb (Box 12)
    - 1976 Mar (Box 12)
    - Apr-May 1976 (Box 12)
    - 1976 Jun (Box 12)
    - Jul-Dec 1976 (Box 12)
    - Jan-Feb 1977 (Box 12)
  - Summary statements - department order, July-December 1973 (Box 12)
  - Summary statements - fund order
    - July-Oct 1973 (Box 12)
    - 1973 Nov (Box 12)
    - 1973 Dec (Box 12)
    - Jan-Feb 1974 (Box 12)
    - Mar-Apr 1974 (Box 12)
    - 1974 May (Box 12)
    - 1974 Jun (Box 12)
- Work papers, 1976-1980; Accession 1984-A-045
  - Audit Workpapers Fiscal 1976 July 1, 1975 to June 30, 1976
- Work papers, audits, and reviews, 1967-1983; Accession 1985-A-027
  - Miscellaneous Work Papers Calendar 1982 Jan 1, 1982 to Dec 31, 1982
  - Construction, Architectural, and Miscellaneous Contracts Reviewed, Fiscal 1980 to Fiscal 1983 July 1 1979 to June 30, 1983
    - Contract Review (Miscellaneous) Fiscal 1980--Forestry School (Box 10, Folder 1137)
    - Architectural and Engineering Contrats, Fiscal 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1138)
    - Architectural and Engineering Contrats, Fiscal 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1139)
    - Construction Contracts, Fiscal 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1140 - 1142)
    - Construction Contracts, Fiscal 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1143 - 1146)
    - Miscellaneous Contracts (Other than Construction), Discal 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1147 - 1148)
    - Architectural and Engineering Contracts, Fiscal 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1149 - 1150)
    - Construction Contracts, Fiscal 1982--Index (Box 11, Folder 1151)
    - Construction Contracts, Fiscal 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1152 - 1157)
    - Construction Contracts, Fiscal 1982 (Box 12, Folder 1158 - 1160)
    - Miscellaneous Contracts (Other than Construction), Fiscal 1982 (Box 12, Folder 1161 - 1162)
    - Hope Building Contract, Fiscal 1982 (Box 12, Folder 1163)
    - Bidding and Contract Results, Fiscal 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1164)
    - Electrical Bid Openings, 1981 to 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1167)
    - Deferred Maintenance--Architectural and Engineering, Fiscal 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1168)
    - Ecklund Termination Clause (Box 12, Folder 1169)
- Audit records, 1971-1972, 1976, 1982; Accession 1985-A-028
  - Yale University Press, Ltd. (U.K.) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Statutory Accounts, 1972 June 30 (Box 1)
  - Management Accounts, 1971 June 30 (Box 1)
  - Cash 01XX (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - WCF's Counted F/1974 and F/1975 (Box 1)
  - External Audit (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yale University Press, Ltd. AR-F/76-20 (Box 1)
  - Review of Yale University Press, Ltd. (Box 1)
  - Fiscal 1976, 1976 March (Box 1)
  - Purchasing Department AR C/1982-53 (955A/B/C/D) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Limited Review of the Purchasing (Box 1)
  - Department Administration Fiscal 1982 (Box 1)
- Audit records, 1974-1983; Accession 1986-A-089
  - Fiscal Year 1975
    - Yale Alumni Fund - Endowment Fund July 1, 1974 - June 30, 1975, January 22, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Year 1979
    - Graduate and Professional Student Senate July 1, 1978 - June 30, 1979, September 19, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Yale Alumni Publications, Inc, July 1, 197and - June 30, 1979, January 11, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Year 1980
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences July 1, 1919 - June 30, 1980, January 13, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Sheffield Scientific School July 1, 1979 - June 30, 1980, September 22, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Yale Alumni Fund - Endowment Fund July 1, 1979 - June 30, 1980, November 22, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Yale Alumni Publications July 1, 1979 - June 30, 1980, March 19, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Yale Summer School of Music and Art, Dec 1, 1919 - Nov 30, 1980, January 30, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8 - 9)
    - Yale Summer School of Music and Art, (Music) Dec 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, January 7, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
    - Yale Summer School of Music and Art, (Music) Dec 1, 1981 - Nov 30, 1982, No Review Date (Box 1, Folder 12 - 13)
    - Yale University Press, July 1, 1979 - June 30, 1980, No Review Date (Box 1, Folder 14 - 20)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Senate July 1, 1979 - June 30, 1980, No Review Date (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, July 1, 1979 to June 30, 1980, September 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22 - 23)
  - Fiscal Year 1981
    - Yale Alumni Fund - Endowment Fund, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, January 12, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27 - 28)
    - Yale University Press, Ltd. London Office, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, November 6, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Yale University Press, New Haven Office, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, September 10, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30 - 37)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Senate 1 of 2, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, January 15, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Senate 2 of 2, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, January 15, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Yale Alumni Publications, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, No Review Date (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Sheffield Scientific, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, December 11, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, January 14, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, Binder 1 July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, September 30, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, Binder 2 July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, September 30, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, Quarter Century Fund July 1, 1980 - June 30, 1981, September 5, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Fiscal Year 1982
    - Graduate Professional Student Senate July 1, 1981 - June 30, 1982, 1982 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Sheffield Scientific School July 1, 1981 - June 10, 1982, December 12, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, July 1, 1981 - June 30, 1982, February 11, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Yale Alumni Fund - Endowment Fund, July 1, 1981 - June 30, 1982, 1981 July - 1982 June (Box 5, Folder 49 - 50)
    - Yale University Press, 1981 July - 1982 June (Box 5, Folder 51 - 58)
    - Yale Alumni Fund - Quarter Century Fund July 1, 1981 - June 30, 1982, September 2, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, July 1, 1981 - June 30, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 60 - 61)
- Work papers, 1967-1984; Accession 1987-A-103
  - Salaries and Wages at G and C fringe benefits rate; 6-30-84 (Final) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Check Signing and destruction control over numbers, signature plates, etc. and miscellaneous problems concerning checks (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Forgeries (through F/77) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Forgeries (F78) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Forgeries (F79) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DHEW: letter of credit audit University of California (F76-78) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - DHEW: Audit of Stockrooms (July 1975) (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - DHEW: Audit of Stockrooms (Aug. 1975) (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - DHEW: Audit.of Stockrooms (3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - DREW: Indirect Cost Rates (Fiscal 1973 and 1974) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - DHEW: Equipment Audit (Fall 1978) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - DHEW: Fiscal 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - DHEW: Fringe Benefits Rates (1973 and 1974) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - DHEW: Various audits, no deficiencies (Jan 1977) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - DREW: Various audits, (Jan 1978) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Federal Government Controls Price, Wage, Energy, etc. (1976) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Associate Treasurer's Office (529G-26-00001-01ZA) Fiscal 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Associate Treasurer's Office (529G-26-00001-01ZA) Fiscal 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bursar's Office (529G-26-00001-01ZA) Fiscal 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bursar's Office (529G-26-00001-01ZA) Fiscal 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bursar's Office (529G-26-00001-01ZA) Fiscal 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Notes Receivable AR/F 80-18 (Review of Notes Receivable) Fiscal 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Accounts Receivable (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Accounts Receivable: review of Campaign for Yale Development Office Outstanding Pledges as at June 30, 1974, Fiscal 1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Same as Folder 8, except Fiscal 1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Same as Folder 8, except Fiscal 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Peabody Museum, WCF 86207 (9520-53) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Data Processing Expense AR C/1982-34 G8G; Integrity Controls of Administrative Data System - Fiscal 1983 (Jan 1982; R. Dorozenski/W. Strohmeyer 0544) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Medical School C/1981 - 9 704A-41; Physiology Dept.; Conflict of Interest - University Employee (Feb 1981; AR Weldon P555) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - G/L System Redesign UA Audit Memo, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - ACMAT-2-1-82 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - OPS 1982-47 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Yale University Press ARC-8!. Review of YUP Computerized Royalty Payments (4/81 D. McGran/A. Weldon) B-039 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Yale University Press committee Minutes (F73 thru F77) PERMANENT FILE (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Yale University Press committee Minutes (F78) PERMANENT FILE (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - External Audit, Fiscal 1980, Yale University Press, Review of Computerized Royalty Payments for Calendar Year Ended Dec 31, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Yale University Press - Property Tax Case Pending (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Grant and Contract Drawdown ARC/82-49 09 and30; Transaction tests review of Federal Fund Drawdowns and Expenditures for Sep 1982 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Interest Income AR/CI981-48 47GA; HHS Audit-Interest Income on Letters of Credit for the Period 7-1-80-6-30-81; Nov 1981 AR Weldbn/WJ Strohmeyer A-18 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Audit Reports and Special Reports, Fiscal 1967 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Audit Reports, Fiscal 1969 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Audit Reports, Fiscal 1970 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Fiscal 1980 - accounting workpapers (Box 5)
  - Alumni Fund - Palo Alto (545E-28-00001-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Engineering andApplied Science (624A-31-00001-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 57 - 58)
  - Physics Department (627B-31-00001-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Office of Professional Service (692P-41-32965-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Medical School - Business Office 690C-41-00001-01ZA (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Yale Psychiatric Institute (742A-41-87058-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Art andArchitecture (776A-44-00001-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Drama School (780A-45-00001-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Same as folder 11 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Microbiology Dept. (WCF 86087) (9100-41) (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Freshman Food Service (945P-61-00001-01ZA) (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Closed Working Cash Funds:
    - Class of 1979 WCF, Alumni Records; 544E-28-75783-01ZA (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Psychology Dept. (WCF 86130) (9200-41) (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Psychology Dept. (WCF 86132) (9220-41) (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Molecular Biophysics (WCF 86021) (616D-31) (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Cash, Review of Dining Hall Working (Fund Number 86041) (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Computer Printouts
    - Fiscal 1982, Yale University Press, Computer Runs (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Yale University Press, Aged Accts Rec. (6-30-83; Binder 8) (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Yale University Press, Inventory Reports, F83; Binder 9 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Records, 1979-1989; Accession 1991-A-067
  - Departmental policies and procedures
    - General, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
    - DHEW Audit of Cost Transfers, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - JSCS Audit, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 6)
    - Corporation AC Meeting Minutes, 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7 - 17)
  - Audit work papers
    - ORM Development Committees, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Associated Student Agencies Permanent File, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Yale University Press, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20 - 24)
    - Yale University Art Gallery, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Soccer Game Tickets, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Football Game Tickets, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Football Parking, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Winter Sports Tickets, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - British Art Center, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Pediatrics, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32 - 33)
    - Central Stockroom, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Library Cash Sales, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 36 - 37)
    - Purchasing Department, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - FICA Refund, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 39 - 40)
    - Central Stockroom, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - MBandB Inventory: Electronics, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - MBandB Inventory: Research, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Dining Hall: China, Silver and Glass, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Salaries and Wages, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Hockey and Basketball Admissions, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - YAA Cash Fund, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Maintenance Expense, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Administrative Data Systems, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 50 - 51)
    - MBandB Inventory: Electronics, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - MBandB Inventory: Research, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Gibbs Laboratory Research, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Pledges, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Moveable Equipment Inventory, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - ADS, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - British Art Center, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Purchasing Department, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 63 - 67)
    - Yale Printing Service Inventory, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Physical Inspection: Harkness Hall, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Bank Accounts, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 74)